Hello friends, how are you, I hope you are doing well,
we are going to do a new project, get a
new suit done, which we have already
talked about in a video, so we are
finally leaving for that today and
Mahesh Bhai is with us and both of them
came to drop us from far away from the village wishing us well, till God, so
what would you like to say
friends, we got scared, I
mean both of them left on both sides, both of them
came till here to drop us, I hope
that we came there with a very good suit,
and this photo shoot has started,
let's ignore the extra petrol, so
stay till the end, now we are finally
leaving from here, this is the photo shoot from the village,
look, it seems
why not take photos, so we are
taking photos, and what about them, they come every day,
we cannot come every day in the cold, we take a bath sometimes, so what do you
mean,
without talking too much nonsense,
let's take you further, we will leave from here, we have to pick up
one more person from Susner, Susner,
after that we will leave for the final location, which is the
block, this is coming after the video came,
you are seeing, we
took Bhai, he delayed it a lot, that's why the cell  Could
not find time and now we have come to
Susner, this brother was a
little unwell, we had
told you in the video, now the
shot is a little better and we will output it, it is not that perfect
also but then we will not make you wait much,
so brother who is lifting,
I
and this Mahesh Bhai are sitting here, we are sitting here, now after having
tea we will leave from here, let's meet at our location
and this is our entire team here and from here
we will go to the next location,
all of them are sitting and the entire time has been passed,
our Mahesh Bhai, Deepu Bhai, Kamal Bhai
and we will go from here
and our shoot will start from tomorrow, so stay tuned till
here, we will show you what else
happens, the rest will meet at the location, so
friends, finally we have reached the location
in this village and this is about 15
kilometers away from Nalkheda, the entire village is empty,
all ruins and there are no houses,
all broken due to summer, our temple was
looking a little good, there is
also a provision of light and white in it, so we came here,
our vehicles were parked, no one lives in the village, there are
one or two houses where people
live, they are also going to leave
and we are going to Nalkheda from this  We made the bed there and
slept here. It's getting
very cold too. We'll start shooting in the morning
because it took a lot of time to
come and make all the arrangements because no
one lives here, so there were
no arrangements, so we came here, there's no
one here, the location is very
dangerous, I mean, there's a lot of noise and the temple.
[Music]
And now we've all arrived at the location and
everyone was feeling hungry, so we thought we'll have dinner for everyone,
then we'll start shooting.
We're sitting here with
all the team members, Kamal Bhaiya, our Mahesh Bhai,
Rakesh Bhai,
everyone is sitting, and we'll all eat here,
after that we'll go to the location, we'll
start shooting here. So,
I'll tell you how the shoot is.
As soon as the shoot starts, we'll show you.
[Music]
And this Kamal ji, we do
n't have our shoot here, so we're passing time. Then
you'll
make the action sequences here.
[Music]
So friends, our shoot is progressing slowly.
[Music] The
video has turned sour, he's saying here, so
hello everyone, how are you all, and the shoot is going on.
Our shoot is going on right now and this is
my Deepu Bhai, this is Bittu Bhai, the
whole team is here and these few people are with us
brother, how are you feeling,
we are also feeling good because it is very
hot, how is the heat, we will
update you in the scene, till then stay tuned,
you can see how hard
we worked and made this shot by using jugaad
[Prasha]
[Music]
Hello everyone, good morning, so today is the
second day of our shoot, yesterday we shot the whole day
and today is the second day of the shoot,
all of them are almost ready
[Music] let's
continue, tomorrow we will continue from where we left off
and me and Rakesh Bhai, both of us were
going on the way, suddenly our petrol has probably finished, the
petrol is making
noise but I don't
know what has happened to the car, it is not starting
and our location is about 1 kilometer ahead